https://www.lib.umn.edu/about/privacy

East Bank
Walter Library (Science & Engineering)
Today:
8:00 a.m.–5:00 p.m.
Health Sciences Library
Today:
8:00 a.m.–5:00 p.m.
Architecture & Landscape Architecture Library
Today:
Closed
Journalism Library (Eric Sevareid)
Today: Closed
Mathematics Library
Today:
Closed
West Bank
Wilson Library
Today:
8:00 a.m.–5:00 p.m.
Elmer L. Andersen Library
Today:
Closed
Law Library
Music Library
Today:
Closed
St. Paul
Magrath Library
Today:
8:00 a.m.–5:00 p.m.
Andersen Horticultural Library (off campus)
Today:
9:00 a.m.–3:00 p.m.
Natural Resources Library
Today:
Closed
Veterinary Medical Library
Today:
Course reserves
Services for...
Unique collections of books, manuscripts, & artifacts
University Digital Conservancy (UDC)
Data services
Digital Arts Sciences & Humanities (DASH)
News
The Libraries welcomes learners and scholars from all cultures and backgrounds.
We are open to all and strive to reflect our community by embracing the diversity of people and ideas.
We commit to providing a safe and accessible environment, and the broadest possible access to information.
We do not tolerate intimidating or disruptive behavior, harassment, or hateful acts.
We are here to assist you. Please do not hesitate to ask for our help.
24/7 Chat
Due to security upgrades, we will no longer support Internet Explorer version 8 or older. Please use a newer browser.
Using the Libraries during COVID-19Four campus libraries are open for Twin Cities students, faculty, and staff with valid U Cards. Hours are limited. Other libraries may be open by appointment. (Last updated Nov. 23, 2020)
Online Privacy Statement
Navigation
About
About us
About our collections
Give to the Libraries
Jobs at the Libraries
Partnerships & grants
Policies
Resources during COVID-19
Strategic plan
Staff directory
Subject librarians
The University of Minnesota respects the privacy of web site visitors to the extent permitted by law. This online privacy statement is intended to inform users of what information is collected by this web site and how the information is used.
Please note that other University of Minnesota web sites may adopt different privacy practices as their specific needs require.
Use of links to other web sites is subject to the privacy statement of the providers of those web sites. We encourage users to be aware when leaving this web site and to read the privacy statement on each web site visited. Often users can tell when they are leaving a University web site by looking at the URL of the destination site.
Contact us with questions about this site’s collection of information or its online privacy statement.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
For security purposes and to ensure that the web site remains available to all users, the University uses software to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
The University collects non-personal information about a user’s Internet connection on this web site, including but not limited to:
the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the name of the Internet domain used to access the Internet
the IP address or URL of the web site from which a user directly linked to this web site
the date and time a user accessed this web site
the pages visited on this web site
the browser and operating system used to access this web site
the search terms used on our search engines
The University uses this non-personal information to help manage the web site and improve service.
This site uses Google Analytics for gathering statistics about web traffic. Information about how Google Analytics gathers and uses data is available in Google’s privacy policy.
Personally Identifiable Information
Some sites and applications provided by the University Libraries record Personally Identifiable Information. We only use these data to provide, improve, and customize services and resources. We use appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our site and periodically update measures with new technologies.
Our data gathering and dissemination are governed by state and federal laws, including the Minnesota Government Data Practices Act, Minnesota Statutes, Chapter 13. Personally identifiable information is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.
Last revised Feb. 2017
Libraries & collections
Ames Library of South Asia
Andersen Library
(
Archives & Special Collections
)
Andersen Horticultural Library (off campus)
Architecture & Landscape Architecture Library
East Asian Library
Government Information
Health Sciences Library
Itasca Biological Station Library (off campus)
Journalism Library (Eric Sevareid)
Walter Library (Science & Engineering)
(Wilson Library front desk)
